599fashion.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy | 599fashion.com

> **Reduce:**
> 
> We understand that there can be concerns about ordering items online. As a leader amongst fashion outlet stores we are proud to share our privacy policy with our customers. It’s important for all retailers, not just online clothing outlet stores, to adhere to and respect the policies set in place to protect our customers’ privacy. Please read below in order to gain further understanding on our policies.
> 
> **Our Commitment to Privacy**
> 
> Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
> 
> **The Information We Collect**
> 
> This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the 599fashion.com website (hereby known as "Site"). On some pages you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include but are not limited to Name, Address, Business Name, Business Address, Email Address, Phone/Fax No, Credit/Debit Card Information, Tax ID No/Sellers Permit No. 
> 
> **The Way We Use Information**
> 
> 599fashion.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this Site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 
> 
> We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 
> 
> **Orders**
> 
> We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 
> 
> We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 
> 
> **Cookies and IP Addresses**
> 
> Cookies may be used with our Site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our Site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our Site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our Site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Site. 
> 
> Some of our business partners may use cookies on our Site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 
> 
> We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 
> 
> **Sharing and Links**
> 
> We may partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 
> 
> This Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that 599fashion.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site, to read the privacy statements of each and every Site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Site. 
> 
> **Subscriptions, Surveys, Contests, Promotions**
> 
> If a user wishes to subscribe to our catalog or newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. 
> 
> From time-to-time our Site requests information from users via surveys, contests, or promotions. Participation in these surveys, contests, or promotions is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this Site. 
> 
> **In Summary**
> 
> Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 
> 
> **Our Commitment to Data Security**
> 
> To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. This Site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Site, your information is protected both online and off-line. 
> 
> **Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**
> 
> Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Site is structured to attract anyone under 13. 
> 
> **How You Can Access or Correct Your Information**
> 
> You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing us a request at [customer service](mailto:info@599fashion.com). We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 
> 
> To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 
> 
> **How to Contact Us**
> 
> If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy or should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, you should first contact 599fashion.com. by [email](mailto:info@599fashion.com).   
>
